Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is red velvet cake.
>> That's as red velvet as it gets.
Delicious.
>> Let me show you how to make it. We're
starting off with a chocolate protein
shake. And then this is the most
important ingredient, red velvet
extract. We're doing a teaspoon of that.
Mixing that up. And then we'll add our
dry ingredients, sweetener, salt,
zantham gum, and then blend that all
together with an immersion blender. Let
this freeze for at least 16 hours. Then
you can take it out, run it under hot
water for about a minute, and then throw
it in your cream on the light ice cream
setting. Now, if you're wondering why
you've never heard of this flavor, it's
because it is in the flavor graveyard,
which is where unpopular flavors go to
die. So, if you want me to remake more
flavors from here, let me know. After
that light ice cream cycle, it might be
a little powdery like this. You can just
go ahead scrape down the sides and throw
it back in on the grease spin setting.
I'm really not sure why they
discontinued this flavor. It seemed to
be extremely popular. If anyone knows
why, let me know down in the comments.
To finish off this flavor, we need some
cake pieces. So, I'm using an Alpha
Prime Bites red velvet brownie. These
things have 19 g of protein and tastes
like a real brownie. This one honestly
just tastes like red velvet cake. We're
just chopping up half of that into
bite-sized pieces, throwing those on
top, and you're good to